<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhaseShift 2017</string>

    <!--ABOUT PHASESHIFT 2017-->
    <string name="aboutPS">PhaseShift is an annual tech symposium of BMS College Of Engineering and is one of the largest of its kind in South India. It encourages budding engineering students to exhibit their talents and demonstrate skills through competitions and workshops. It aims to coalesce ideas from industry in order to achieve high level of skill to help the students emerge as globally competent professionals. Participation of many industry experts and professionals creates a congenial atmosphere that knits learning and fun. By embracing technology, Phase Shift organises a plethora of events collaborated with industries that provides a neat paradigm to encourage technological advances through seminars, workshops, competitions and multidisciplinary events. By doing so, the sponsors get to influence people and work miracles. This not only helps to spread the ideology behind each event but also helps the sponsors get more publicity with our unique strategy for the same. They are assured of a huge benefit from the exposure to a large and diverse crowd that PhaseShift attracts.</string>
    <string name="aboutOrganizationalFramework">PhaseShift is an annual tech symposium of BMS College Of Engineering and is one of the largest of its kind in South India. It encourages budding engineering students to exhibit their talents and demonstrate skills through competitions and workshops. It aims to coalesce ideas from industry in order to achieve high level of skill to help the students emerge as globally competent professionals. Participation of many industry experts and professionals creates a congenial atmosphere that knits learning and fun. By embracing technology, Phase Shift organises a plethora of events collaborated with industries that provides a neat paradigm to encourage technological advances through seminars, workshops, competitions and multidisciplinary events. By doing so, the sponsors get to influence people and work miracles. This not only helps to spread the ideology behind each event but also helps the sponsors get more publicity with our unique strategy for the same. They are assured of a huge benefit from the exposure to a large and diverse crowd that PhaseShift attracts.</string>
    <string name="aboutBMSCE">BMS College of Engineering, Bengaluru was founded in the year 1946 by Late Sri B.M.Sreenivasaiah, a great visionary and philanthropist and nurtured by his son Late Sri B.S. Narayan. BMSCE is the first private sector initiative from the erstwhile state of Mysore towards engineering education in India. Started with only three undergraduate courses, BMSCE today offers 13 undergraduate and 16 postgraduate courses both in conventional and engineering areas. Fifteen of its departments are recognised as Research Centres offering PhD/M.Sc. (Engineering by Research) degrees in Science, Engineering, Architecture and Management. Modernisation, expansion and sophistication have not changed the basic philosophy of education at BMSCE.</string>
    <string name="aboutBMSCEMore">BMSCE is the first institution in the state to be bestowed with NBA Accreditation in Tier-I format(Washington Accord) for UG programs. It is a beneficiary of TEQIP Phase I and II(Technical Education Quality Improvement Programme, under World Bank Assistance) with an established Centre of Excellence in the Area of Advanced Materials. Accredited with A grade by NAAC with CGPA of 3.14/4.00. Approved by Council of Architecture (COA), New Delhi. BMSCE is currently ranked first in the state of Karnataka,14th among top 150 Engineering Institutions in India as per the Times Engineering Institutes Ranking Survey 2016.</string>
    <string name="aboutPSOutcomes">The ability to, \n\u25CF\tDeploy the skills acquired for development of prototypes in support of ideas using latest technologies.\n\u25CF\tInitiate connects for sustained partnerships with organisations of diverse interests that may lead to establishment of further enterprises.\n\u25CF\tWork with multidisciplinary teams towards a common goal.\n\u25CF\tOrganise and manage the un-foreseen operational challenges.</string>

    <!--NAVIGATION-->
    <string name="title_schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="title_events">Events</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_map">Map</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="shortDescription">Description</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>


</resources>
